tabelog.us 2014-11-26

# Tabélog New York

Last modified: Sep 15, 2012

### Introduction

Tabélog, Inc. (" **Company** " or " **We** ") respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website http://www.tabelog.us/ (our " **Website** ") and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * On this Website.
  * In e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and this Website.
  * Through mobile applications, which provide dedicated non-browser-based interaction between you and this Website.

It does not apply to information collected by:

  * us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Company or any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries); or
  * any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website

The Website may collect information regarding restaurants or Users representing restaurants through such Users’ offline correspondence.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time. (see Changes to our [Privacy Policy](http://www.tabelog.us/privacy_policy/index)) Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

### Children Under the Age of 13

Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features/register on the Website, or otherwise use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at:

Tabélog, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy Officer  
54 West 40th Street #424  
New York, NY 10018, USA  

### Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:

  * by which you may be personally identified, such as name, username, photograph from Facebook, postal address, e-mail address (" **personal information** ");
  * that is about you but individually does not identify you, such as nationality, gender, postal code, occupation, annual income, and date of birth; and/or
  * about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details.

We collect this information:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.
  * Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses and information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies.
  * From third parties, for example, our business partners, such as Facebook.

### Information You Provide to Us.

The information we collect on or through our Website may include:

  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses), if you contact us.
  * Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.
  * Your search queries on the Website.

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, " **posted** ") on public areas of the Website or third parties (collectively, " **User Contributions** "). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Although we limit access to certain pages/you may set certain privacy settings for such information by logging into your account profile, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

### Usage Details, IP Addresses and Cookies.

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may automatically collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns, including:

  * Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, browser type, user agent, cookie information and referrer.

A user agent is software acting on behalf of you, the user. A referrer identifies the origin of the User traffic before coming to Tabélog (i.e., another webpage) 

The information we collect automatically is statistical data, and does not identify any individual. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service by enabling us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
  * Speed up your searches.
  * Recognize you when you return to our Website.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection includes Cookies.

A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website. 

We do not collect personal information automatically, but we may tie this information to personal information about you that we collect from other sources or you provide to us.

### How We Use Your Information

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

  * To provide user authentication during the login process.
  * To present our Website and its contents to you.
  * To provide you with information, products or services of the Company or its Affiliates by postal mail, telephone, electronic mail or other means.
  * To process information into anonymized information to create statistical data to use for promoting the use of the Company’s services
  * To contact you, if necessary, in connection with the Website, an in particular any changes to our Website or Terms of Use.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

### Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
  * To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of the Company's assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by the Company about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply our [Terms of Use](http://www.tabelog.us/terms_of_use) and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes, as appropriate.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

### Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

  * Tracking Technologies and Advertising. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe's website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly (e.g., logging in).
  * Promotional Offers from the Company. If you do not wish to have your e-mail address used by the Company to promote our services, you can opt-out by checking the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data or at any other time by logging into the Website and adjusting your user preferences in your account profile by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by sending us an e-mail stating your request to . If we have sent you a promotional e-mail, you may send us a return e-mail asking to be omitted from future e-mail distributions. Furthermore, you may choose not to receive promotional emails from Tabélog by unchecking the associated box on your [MyPage site](https://ssl.tabelog.us/my/profile/edit).

### Accessing and Correcting Your Information

You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Website and visiting your account profile page on the MyPage section of the Website.

You may also send us an e-mail at  to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

If we delete your User Contributions from the Website at our sole discretion in accordance with our terms of use, copies of your User Contributions may still remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users. Proper access and use of information provided on the Website, including User Contributions, is governed by our [Terms of Use](http://www.tabelog.us/terms_of_use).

### Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to  or write us at:

Tabélog, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy Officer  
54 West 40th Street #424  
New York, NY 10018, USA  

### Data Security

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. Information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where you have chosen a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Website like message boards. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Website.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users' personal information, we may choose to notify you by e-mail to the primary e-mail address specified in your account and/or through a notice on the Website home page.

The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. The policy may be revised from time to time in the Company’s sole discretion, so Users should check back frequently. Users may view a new policy, along with a link to prior version of the policy. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

Contact Information

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:

Tabélog, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy Officer  
54 West 40th Street #424  
New York, NY 10018, USA
